Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music collection
  - 12 inch vinyl
    - Numbered by Bambaataa
      - 509 - For all we know, 1976; SR-9179; Phillips, Esther, 1935-1984. (Box 116)
        Kristin Records
      - 510 - Car Wash: the original motion picture soundtrack, 1976; SR-8239-8240; Whitfield, Norman. (Box 116)
        MCA Records
      - 511 - Unfinished business., 1976; SR-8241-8242 (Box 116)
      - 512 - Hardcore jollies, 1976; SR-9180; Clinton, George. (Box 116)
      - 513 - Promised heights., 1974; SR-9181; Cymande (Musical group) (Box 116)
      - 514 - Bloodshot, 1973; SR-8243-8244; J. Geils Band. (Box 117)
      - 515 - Brazil, 1975; SR-8245-8246; Coco (Musical group) (Box 117)
        Avi Records
      - 515 - Brazil, Coco (Musical group) (Box 117)
      - 516 - Heard ya missed me, well I'm back, 1976; SR-9182-9183; Stone, Sly. (Box 117)
      - 516 - Heard ya missed me, well I'm back, Stone, Sly. (Box 117)
      - 517 - Open sesame (Groove with the genie); Love & understanding (come together), 1976; SR-8247-8248; Kool & the Gang. (Box 117)
      - 518 - Disco magic (pt. 1); Disco magic (pt. 2), 1976; SR-8249; T-Connection (Musical group) (Box 117)
      - 520 - On the road again, 1976; SR-8250; Rogers, D. J., 1948- (Box 117)
        Demonstration, not for sale copy.
      - 521 - Dance and shake your tambourine, 1976; SR-8251; Universal Robot Band. (Box 117)
        Red Greg Records
        Bronx, New York
      - 525 - Frampton comes alive, 1976; SR-8252-8253; Frampton, Peter. (Box 117)
      - 526 - High energy, 1976; SR-8254-8255; Holland, Brian. (Box 117)
      - 529 - When love is new; All I need is you tonight, 1976; SR-9565-9566; Prysock, Arthur. (Box 117)
        Ode Records
      - 530 - Truck Turner: original soundtrack from the American International release, 1974; SR-8256; Hayes, Isaac. (Box 117)
      - 530 - Truck Turner: original soundtrack from the American International release, 1974; SR-6935-SR-6936; Hayes, Isaac. (Box 6)
        ENew Jerseyoy Records
      - 531 - Soul on your side, 1976; SR-8257; Rhythm Makers (Musical group) (Box 117)
        Vigor Records
      - Soul on your side, 1976; SR-8258; Rhythm Makers (Musical group) (Box 117)
        Not numbered, housed with SR-8257
      - 532 - My love is free; It don't have to be funky (to be a groove), 1976; SR-8259; Double Exposure (Musical group) (Box 117)
        Salsoul Records
      - 533 - Kalakuta show, 1976; SR-9184; Fela, 1938-1997. (Box 117)
        Makossa
      - 535 - Billy Preston., 1976; SR-9185; Preston, Billy. (Box 117)
      - 536 - Feel it., 1976; SR-8260 (Box 117)
        WMOT Records
      - 536 - Feel it., 1976; SR-8261 (Box 117)
      - 537 - Born to get down, 1976; SR-8262; Muscle Shoals Horns. (Box 117)
      - 538 - Dancing machine., 1974; SR-8263-8264; Jackson 5 (Musical group) (Box 117)
      - 538 - Dancing machine., Jackson 5 (Musical group) (Box 117)
      - 541 - Disco duck, 1976; SR-8265; Disco Duck Symphony. (Box 117)
        Matrix / Runout (A-Side Runout Etching): BJ DISCO 1003 A Best TM/JR; Matrix / Runout (B-Side Runout Etching): BJ DISCO 1003 B Best TM/JR.
      - 542 - Joyful jukebox music., 1976; SR-8266-8267; Jackson 5 (Musical group) (Box 117)
      - 542 - Joyful jukebox music., Jackson 5 (Musical group) (Box 117)
      - 543 - Gittin' off, 1976; SR-8268; Bohannon, Hamilton. (Box 117)
      - 546 - Dancing queen; In the morning, 1976; SR-8269; Douglas, Californiarol. (Box 117)
      - 547 - Let's go down to the disco; You + me + love., 1976; SR-8270 (Box 117)
        Whitfield Records
      - 548 - Funk de mambo: (dance to the music), 1976; SR-8271-8272; Andrews, Reggie, (Box 117)
        "Promotional. Not for sale."
        Horizon
      - 549 - Get up and dance; Don't abuse it, 1976; SR-8273; Memphis Horns. (Box 117)
        RCA Records
      - 550 - Turn on to love, 1976; SR-8274; Jumbo (Musical group) (Box 117)
        Pye Records
      - 551 - Midnight love affair, 1976; SR-8276 (Box 117)
      - 551 - Midnight love affair, 1976; SR-8275 (Box 117)
      - 552 - Con-Funk-Shun., 1976; SR-8277; Con-Funk-Shun (Musical group) (Box 117)
      - 553 - My sweet summer suite., 1976; SR-9186; White, Barry, 1944-2003. (Box 117)
      - 554 - Dr. Buzzard's Original "Savannah" Band., 1976; SR-8278; Darnell, August. (Box 117)
      - 555 - Listen to the Buddha, 1976; SR-9187; O¿¿zo¿¿ (Musical group) (Box 117)
        Disneyland
      - 557 - Cheo's rainbow, 1976; SR-9188; Feliciano, Cheo. (Box 117)
        Vaya Records
      - 558 - Little drummer boy: special disco version; Sweet Georgia Brown, 1975; SR-8279 (Box 118)
      - Little drummer boy: special disco version; Sweet Georgia Brown, 1975; SR-8280 (Box 118)
        Not numbered, housed with SR-8279
        Pickwick International Productions
      - 560 - Elementary, 1976; SR-8281; Ragin, Melvin. (Box 118)
      - 561 - Mystique., 1977; SR-8282; Mystique (Musical group) (Box 118)
      - 562 - Nuevo Navidad, 1976; SR-9189; Nazario, Ednita. (Box 118)
        Borinquen
        Puerto Rico
      - 563 - Music fuh ya' = Musica para tu, 1977; SR-9190; Taj Mahal (Musician), (Box 118)
      - 564 - Gotta get it, 1975; SR-8283; Tony Valor Sounds Orchestra. (Box 118)
      - 565 - Passport to ecstasy, 1977; SR-8284; Hampton, Californiarl. (Box 118)
      - 566 - Catfish, 1976; SR-8285; Four Tops (Musical group) (Box 118)
      - 567 - Message in the music, 1976; SR-8286; O'Jays (Musical group) (Box 118)
      - 568 - Enchantment, 1976; SR-8287; Enchantment (Musical group) (Box 118)
      - 569 - Solid, 1976; SR-8288; Henderson, Michael, 1951- (Box 118)
      - 570 - Real Thing., 1976; SR-8289; Real Thing (Musical group) (Box 118)
      - 572 - Second breath, 1976; SR-8290; LaSalle, Denise. (Box 118)
      - 573 - Mary, Scherrie & Susaye, 1976; SR-8291; Supremes (Musical group) (Box 118)
      - 573 - Mary, Scherrie & Susaye, 1976; SR-8292; Supremes (Musical group) (Box 118)
      - 574 - Shake it, shake it, 1976; SR-8293; Hutch, Willie. (Box 118)
      - 575 - Please, Manila Thriller (Box 118)
      - 576 - Kitsch, 1975; SR-8294-8295; Randy Pie (Musical group) (Box 118)
      - 577 - Earth mover, 1976; SR-8296; Mason, Harvey, 1947- (Box 118)
        White label; promotional copy.
      - 577 - Please, Manila Thriller (Box 118)
      - 578 - Kalyan., 1977; SR-8297-8298; Kalyan (Musical group) (Box 118)
      - 582 - Tales of Kidd Funkadelic, 1976; SR-9191; Funkadelic (Musical group) (Box 118)
      - 583 - Diamond touch, 1976; SR-8299; McCrae, George. (Box 118)
        Promotional copy; white label._x000D_
      - 585 - Thou shalt boogie forever, 1976; SR-8300; Sins of Satan (Musical group) (Box 118)
      - 586 - Disco inferno, 1976; SR-8301; Trammps (Musical group), (Box 118)
      - 587 - Feel the beat (everybody disco), 1976; SR-8302; Ohio Players (Musical group) (Box 118)
      - 588 - Magic's in the air; Boy, I really tied one on, 1976; SR-8303-8304; Phillips, Esther, 1935-1984. (Box 118)
        Kudu
      - 589 - Ahh ... the name is Bootsy, baby!, 1977; SR-9192; Collins, William, 1952- (Box 118)
      - 589 - Sound of Africa, 1975; SR-8305; Uhuru Dance Band. (Box 118)
        Agoro Records
      - 590 (jacket) - Shaft in Africa, 1973; SR-6773; Pate, Johnny, (Box 2)
      - 590 (jacket) - Shaft in Africa, 1973; SR-6833; Pate, Johnny, (Box 3)
      - 591 - Everybody likes some kind of music, 1973; SR-9193; Preston, Billy. (Box 118)
      - 591 - Everybody likes some kind of music, 1973; SR-8306; Preston, Billy. (Box 118)
      - 592 - Everybody come on out, 1976; SR-8307; Turrentine, Stanley. (Box 118)
      - 593 - Everything must change, 1976; SR-9194; Crawford, Randy. (Box 118)
      - 594 - Free and in love, 1976; SR-9195; Jackson, Millie. (Box 118)
      - 595 - Evening with Diana Ross., 1977; SR-9196-9197; Ross, Diana, 1944- (Box 118)
      - 596 - What you need, 1976; SR-8308; Side Effect (Musical group) (Box 118)
      - 597 - I don't know what's on your mind, 1976; SR-8309; Spiders Webb (Musical group) (Box 118)
      - I don't know what's on your mind, 1976; SR-8480; Spiders Webb (Musical group) (Box 118)
        Not numbered, housed with SR-8309. D.J. copy; not for sale._x000D_
      - 600 - D.J. Rogers., 1975; SR-8310; Rogers, D. J., 1948- (Box 118)
        Shelter Recording Co.
      - 600 - D.J. Rogers., Rogers, D. J., 1948- (Box 118)
      - 601 - Stranger in the city, 1976; SR-8311; Miles, John (Vocalist) (Box 118)
      - 602 - Sit on it!, 1977; SR-8312; Smith, Jimmy. (Box 118)
      - 604 - Ha cha cha (Funktion); Sambo (Progression); Screwed (Conditions); What's on your mind (Expression), 1976; SR-8313; Brass Construction (Musical group) (Box 118)
        "Special disco record" DJ use only._x000D_ From the Brass Construction II album, UA LA677 G on United Artists Records.
      - 605 - Twenty-four hours a day, 1977; SR-8314; Pennington, Barbara. (Box 119)
        DJ use only; not for sale._x000D_ "Special disco record."
      - 608 - Madhouse, 1976; SR-9198; Levay, Silvester. (Box 119)
      - 609 - After hours 77', 1977; SR-8316; Medley, Phil. (Box 119)
        Promotional copy; not for sale.
        Pyramid
      - 609 - After hours 77', 1977; SR-8315; Medley, Phil. (Box 119)
      - 610 - You're what's missing in my life, 1977; SR-8317; Cameron, G. C. (Box 119)
      - 611 - Standing up for love, 1977; SR-9199 (Box 119)
      - 612 - Let me ride, 1977; SR-8318; Windy City (Musical group) (Box 119)
        Chi-Sound
      - 613 - Man to man, 1976; SR-8319; Hot Chocolate (Musical group: 1970-) (Box 119)
      - 614 - Power of music, 1976; SR-8320; Miracles (Musical group) (Box 119)
      - 615 - Masters in Philadelphia, 1977; SR-8321-8322; Philarmonics. (Box 119)
      - 616 - Moods and grooves, 1976; SR-8323; Ju-Par Universal Orchestra. (Box 119)
        Juana
      - 617 - Atmosphere strut, 1976; SR-8324; Cloud One (Musical group) (Box 119)
        P&P Records
      - 619 - Juicy fruit (disco freak), 1976; SR-9200; Hayes, Isaac. (Box 119)
      - 620 - Dionne., 1976; SR-8325-8326; Warwick, Dionne. (Box 119)
        Additional no. on label: Lake Shore Music LSM-992.
        Springboard International Records
      - 622 - Boogie beat '77, 1976; SR-8327; Sparrow (Calypso singer) (Box 119)
      - 623 - Love in 'c' minor, 1977; SR-8328; Heart and Soul Orchestra. (Box 119)
      - 624 - Rigor mortis, 1975; SR-8330; Cameo (Musical group) (Box 124)
        "Special disco version - one sided record". "Promotional copy - Not for sale"--Disc label.
      - 627 - Uptown festival, 1977; SR-8331; Shalamar (Musical group) (Box 119)
      - 628 - Native New Yorker (disco version); Easy come, easy go; Hold de mota down, 1977; SR-8332; Odyssey (Musical group) (Box 119)
      - Vicki Sue Robinson., 1976; SR-9329; Robinson, Vicki Sue. (Box 119)
        Not numbered, housed with SR-9330.
      - 628 - Daylight, 1976; SR-9330; Robinson, Vicki Sue. (Box 119)
        "Not for Sale."_x000D__x000D_From the "Vicki Sue Robinson" album, APL1-1829.
      - 629 - Share it; Ain't nothing but a party, 1976; SR-8333; Tribe (Funk group) (Box 119)
        Fantasy/WMOT Records
      - 630 - Funk Machine., 1976-1977; SR-8334-8335; Funk Machine (Musical group) (Box 119)
      - 632 - Get happy; It's your sweet love, 1977; SR-8336-8337; Horne, Jimmy Bo. (Box 119)
      - 633 - Ojah awake, 1976; SR-8338 (Box 119)
      - 633 - Ojah awake, 1976; SR-8339 (Box 119)
      - 634 - Strut 'n' get up; Freeze it up, 1976; SR-8340-8341; Lee, John, 1952- (Box 119)
        "DJ use only. Not for sale."
      - 634 - I'm in heaven: (disco version), 1975; SR-8342; Steals, Melvin, (Box 119)
        "Not for sale."_x000D_
      - 635 - Rhythms of the world; Soul cha cha; That's the joint, 1976; SR-8343-8344; McCoy, Van, (Box 119)
        "Disco mix."_x000D_ "Promotion Copy, Not for sale."
        H&L Records
        Englewood Cliffs, New Jersey
      - 635 - Subsitute, 1978; SR-8345; Gaynor, Gloria. (Box 119)
        Track title was actually "Substitute" but misspelled as "Subsitute" on the label._x000D_ Stereo editions with white labels stating "Promotional Copy"._x000D_
      - 636 - Caribbean disco; Oh girl, 1977; SR-8346; Sax, Bobby. (Box 119)
        "Promotional copy"--Label on jacket._x000D_ Matrix / Runout (Run-Out Inscription A-Side): ABET-69469-A DP/WOODLAND AD7; Matrix / Runout (Run-Out Inscription B-Side): ABET-69469-B DP/WOODLAND AD7.
        Abet: Distributed by Nashboro Record Co.
        Nashville, Tennessee
      - 637 - Get up and dance, 1977; SR-8347; John, Elton. (Box 119)
        Promotional copy._x000D_ Pressed on blue vinyl, issued in a blue custom title sleeve.
      - 638 - Finger lickin good, 1975; SR-8348-8349 (Box 119)
      - 639 - There's music in the air., 1976; SR-8350; Mbulu, Letta. (Box 119)
      - 641 - Commodores (Box 119)
      - 642 - B-oo-g-ie; Feel like dancin', 1977; SR-8351; Sain, Oliver. (Box 119)
        "Promotional copy"
      - 643 - Players'Association., 1977; SR-8352; Players Association (Musical group) (Box 119)
        Vanguard
      - 644 - Sweet exorcist, 1974; SR-9201; Mayfield, Curtis. (Box 119)
      - 645 - Electrified funk., 1977; SR-8353 (Box 119)
      - 646 - Morning, Noon & Night., 1977; SR-8354; Morning, Noon & Night (Musical group) (Box 119)
        United Artists/Roadshow
      - 647 - Shanty town determination, 1977; SR-9202; Trinity (Musician) (Box 119)
        TR International
        Jamaica
      - 648 - Do what you wanna do (disco version); Got to see my lady, 1977; SR-8355; T-Connection (Musical group) (Box 119)
      - 650 - Get your boom, boom (around the room), 1977; SR-8356; Pamplemousse (Musical group) (Box 119)
      - 651 - Original disco-mix., 1970-1979; SR-8357 (Box 120)
        Dirt Style Records
      - 653 - Blow for me, a toot to you, 1977; SR-9203 (Box 120)
      - 654 - Accept no substitutes, 1976; SR-8358; Pleasure (Musical group), (Box 120)
      - 655 - Mahogany: a Paramount picture, 1975; SR-8359; Masser, Michael. (Box 120)
      - 655 - Mahogany: a Paramount picture, 1975; SR-8360; Masser, Michael. (Box 120)
      - 656 - Celi Bee & The Buzzy Bunch., 1977; SR-8361; Celi Bee. (Box 120)
        APA
      - 657 - Any way you like it, 1976; SR-8362; Houston, Thelma. (Box 120)
      - 658 - Return of the Incredible Bongo Band., 1974; SR-9204-9205 (Box 120)
        Pride Records
      - 659 - Kongmania., 1977; SR-8363 (Box 120)
        Curtom Records: Distributed by Warner Bros. Records
      - 660 - Only hits, 1973; SR-8364-8365; Ventures (Musical group) (Box 120)
        "UA-LA147-G2" on inside of fold-out jacket._x000D_ "SVBB-95230"--Label.
      - 661 - Now do u wanta dance, 1977; SR-9206; Graham Central Station (Musical group) (Box 120)
      - 662 - I hope we get to love in time, 1976; SR-9207; McCoo, Marilyn. (Box 120)
      - 663 - Short trip to space, 1977; SR-8366; Tropea (Musical group) (Box 120)
        Marlin; Distributed by T.K. Productions
      - 664 - Magic, 1977; SR-8367; T-Connection (Musical group) (Box 120)
        Dash Records,
      - 665 - Voodounon, 1974; SR-8368-8369; Lafayette Afro Rock Band. (Box 120)
        ECM Records
      - 666 - Mother Focus., 1975; SR-8370; Focus (Musical group) (Box 120)
      - 667 - Snake, 1972; SR-9208; Exuma. (Box 120)
      - 668 - Yesterday's dreams, 1976; SR-8371; Johnson, Alphonso. (Box 120)
      - 669 - Simply Carrie., 1977; SR-8372 (Box 120)
      - 670 - Go for your guns, 1977; SR-8373; Isley Brothers. (Box 120)
      - Livin' in the life, 1977; SR-9641; Isley Brothers. (Box 120)
        Not numbered, housed with SR-8374. "Demonstration, Not for Sale."_x000D_ "Taken from the T-Neck LP: Go for your guns, PZ 34432
        T-Neck Records: Distributed by Columbia Records
      - 671 - Energizer, 1977; SR-8374; Touch (Musical group) (Box 120)
        Demonstration, not for sale.
      - 672 - My cherie amour; All my life (I wanna live with you), 1977; SR-8375-8376; Soul Train Gang (Musical group) (Box 120)
        B-Side From "The Soul Train Gang" Album, BVL1-1844.
      - 672 - My cherie amour; All my life (I wanna live with you), Soul Train Gang (Musical group) (Box 120)
      - 675 - Tea dance: the original New York cast recording, 1976; SR-8377; LaRue, D. C. (Box 120)
      - 676 - Totally Ta¿¿ta, 1977; SR-8376; Vega, Ta¿¿ta. (Box 120)
      - 677 - Motown's preferred stock: stock option no. 2., 1973; SR-8379 (Box 120)
      - 678 - Motown's preferred stock: stock option no. 3., 1977; SR-8380 (Box 120)
      - 679 - Hit it again, 1977; SR-8381; Tornader (Musical group) (Box 120)
      - 679 - Hit it again, 1977; SR-8382; Tornader (Musical group) (Box 120)
      - 681 - Sunbear., 1977; SR-8383-8384; Sunbear (Musical group) (Box 120)
        Soul Train Records
      - 681 - Sunbear., Sunbear (Musical group) (Box 120)
      - 682 - Iguac¿¿u, 1977; SR-8385; Passport (Musical group) (Box 120)
      - 683 - Sweet dynamite, 1977; SR-8386; Barry, Claudja. (Box 120)
      - 686 - Uptown festival, 1977; SR-8387; Shalamar (Musical group) (Box 120)
      - 687 - Got to give it up, 1977; SR-8388; Gaye, Marvin. (Box 141)
        Promotional copy released in white cardboard sleeve with black titles._x000D_ For disco use only; not for sale._x000D_
      - 688 - Exclusively yours, 1977; SR-8389; Grody, Gordon. (Box 120)
      - 689 - Trans-Europe express, Kraftwerk (Box 120)
      - 691 - Instant Coffey, 1974; SR-8390; Coffey, Dennis. (Box 120)
      - 692 - Contradiction, 1976; SR-9209; Ohio Players (Musical group) (Box 120)
      - 693 - Magic bird of fire; Getaway, 1977; SR-8391; Salsoul Orchestra. (Box 120)
      - 694 - Eleven sides of Baker, 1977; SR-8392; Baker, Ginger. (Box 120)
        Sire Records
      - 695 - Action is tight, 1977; SR-8393; Calypso Rose. (Box 121)
        Charlie's Records
      - 696 - Cerrone's paradise, 1977; SR-8394; Cerrone. (Box 121)
        Malligator
      - 697 - Original disco duck., 1977; SR-8395; Dees, Rick. (Box 121)
      - 698 - Man and a woman, 1977; sr-8396-8397; Hayes, Isaac. (Box 121)
      - 699 - Lullaby of Broadway, 1977; SR-8398; I.R.T. (Musical group) (Box 121)
      - 700 - Disco symphony., 1977; SR-8399; Camouflage (Disco group) (Box 121)
        Hit Makers of America; Distributed nationally by Queen Constance Records
      - 701 - Super trick: Bull City party, 1977; SR-8400; N.C.C.U. (Musical group) (Box 121)
      - 702 - Philly Armada; For the love of money, 1977; SR-8401; Armada Orchestra. (Box 121)
      - 703 - Seven minutes of funk; Ain't nothing but something to do, 1976; SR-8402; Whole Darn Family (Musical group) (Box 121)
        Soul International Records
      - 704 - I've got to dance (To keep from cryin'); The hustle and the bus stop, 1977; SR-8403; Destinations (Disco group) (Box 121)
      - 705 - Ghetto disco, 1977; SR-8404; Taylor, Ted, 1934-1987. (Box 121)
        Promotional copy; white label.
      - 706 - Everybody dance, 1977; SR-8405; Bumblebee Unlimited (Musical group) (Box 121)
      - 707 - Let's do the Latin hustle, 1977; SR-8406-8407; Drennon, Eddie. (Box 121)
        Friends & Co.
      - 708 - Lovin' is really my game; Stormin', 1977; SR-8408-8409; Brainstorm (Musical group) (Box 121)
        Promotional copy; white label._x000D_ Tabu: JD-10963; additional no.: QD-10963._x000D_
        Tabu
      - 709 - You are the star, 1976; SR-8410; Jakki (Musical group) (Box 121)
        West End Records
      - 711 - Ten per cent", 1976; SR-8411; Double Exposure (Musical group) (Box 121)
        Limited edition._x000D_
      - 712 - Nice 'n' naasty; Salsoul 3001, 1976; SR-8412; Salsoul Orchestra. (Box 121)
      - 713 - Earth creature, 1974; SR-8413-8414; Knight, Boobie. (Box 121)
      - 713 - Earth creature, Knight, Boobie. (Box 121)
      - 714 - Work song, 1977; SR-8415-8416; Lundy, Pat. (Box 121)
      - 714 - 4, 1981; SR-7009; Foreigner (Musical group), (Box 16)
        Promotional copy._x000D_ From the Atlantic LP 16999, Foreigner 4._x000D_
      - 715 - Magic journey., 1977; SR-8417; Salsoul Orchestra. (Box 121)
      - 716 - Melting pot, 1971; SR-8418; Booker T. & the MG's (Musical group) (Box 121)
        Promotion copy; white label.
      - 718 - Journey into love, 1977; SR-8419-8420; Kebekelektrik (Musical group) (Box 121)
        LAX Records
      - 720 - Tonight's the night, Knight, Bobby and the Universal Lady (Box 121)
      - 719 - Encyclopedia of rock & roll: 100 super hits. Record five., 1978; SR-8425 (Box 121)
        TVP Records: TVP-1009 (SLX-01934-35).
        TVP Records
      - 719 - Encyclopedia of rock & roll: 100 super hits. Records 1 & 2., 1976; SR-8421-8422 (Box 121)
        TVP Records: TVP-1009 (SLX-01926/29).
      - 719 - Encyclopedia of rock & roll: 100 super hits. Records 3 & 4., 1977; SR-8423-8424 (Box 121)
        TVP Records: TVP-1009 (SLX-01930/33).
      - 722 - Autobahn, 1974; SR-8426; Kraftwerk (Musical group) (Box 121)
        Vertigo
      - 723 - Express yourself; Have a good time, 1977; SR-6909; New York Community Choir. (Box 6)
        This copy used on the Renegades of Rhythm Tour. Promotional copy.
      - 724 - Hot., 1977; SR-9210; Hot (Musical group) (Box 121)
        "Promotional copy - not for sale"
      - 725 - Make it with you; You are number one, 1977; SR-9331 (Box 121)
        From the Open up your love album (BVL1-2270)._x000D_ "Not for sale."
      - 726 - Miss Broadway, 1977; SR-9211; Belle Epoque (Musical group) (Box 121)
        Carrere
      - 727 - Rockets., 1976; SR-9212; Rockets (Musical group: France) (Box 121)
      - 727 - Rockets., Rockets (Musical group: France) (Box 121)
      - 729 - Hit and run; We're getting stronger (the longer we stay together), 1977; SR-8427; Holloway, Loleatta. (Box 121)
        "From the Gold Mind LP GZS-7500 "Loleatta"."
        Gold Mind Records
      - 730 - Radio-activity., 1975; SR-8428; Kraftwerk (Musical group) (Box 121)
      - 732 - Cooley High., 1975; SR-8429-8430 (Box 121)
      - 732 - Cooley High., 1975; SR-8431-8432 (Box 121)
      - 733 - Devil's gun, 1977; SR-8433; C.J. & Co. (Musical group) (Box 121)
      - 733 - Devil's gun, 1977; SR-8434; C.J. & Co. (Musical group) (Box 121)
        Westbound Records; Distributed by Atlantic Records
      - 734 - Shut out, 1977; SR-8435; Jabara, Paul. (Box 121)
        Pressed on clear red vinyl._x000D_
        Casablanca Record and FilmWorks
      - 734 - Black grass; I feel like dancing, 1972; SR6807-6808; Bad Bascomb (Musical group) (Box 3)
        Paramount Records
      - 735 - Discomania, 1977; SR-8436-8437; Valentinos. (Box 121)
      - 736 - Spandisco., 1977; SR-8438 (Box 121)
        Midsong International
      - Oye como va; Medley: Spanish Harlem, Dancin' to SpanDisco, 1977; SR-8439 (Box 118)
        Not numbered, housed with SR-8438. From the "SpanDisco" album, BKL1-2292.
      - 737 - Deep: music from the original motion picture soundtrack, 1977; SR-8440; Barry, John, 1933-2011. (Box 121)
        Pressed on blue transparent vinyl.
      - 738 - Disco calypso, 1977; SR-8441; Becket. (Box 121)
      - 738 - Disco calypso, 1977; SR-8442; Becket, (Box 121)
        "Promotional copy. Not for sale."
      - 739 - Hold tight; Turn the beat around, 1976-1977; SR-8443-8444; Robinson, Vicki Sue. (Box 121)
        "Not for Sale."_x000D_
      - 740 - Carry on, turn me on; Tango in space, 1977; SR-8445-8446; Ecama, 1953- (Box 122)
      - 740 - Love and Kisses., 1977; SR-8447 (Box 122)
      - 742 - Hit man, 1975; SR-8448; Kendricks, Eddie. (Box 122)
      - 743 - Osmonds "live"., 1972; SR-8449-8450; Osmonds (Musical group) (Box 122)
      - 744 - Nytro., 1977; SR-8451 (Box 122)
      - 746 - African queens, 1977; SR-8452; Ritchie Family (Musical group) (Box 122)
        Marlin
      - 748 - Blackbyrds., 1974; SR-8453; Blackbyrds (Musical group) (Box 122)
      - 749 - Back home, 1977; SR-8454; Coffey, Dennis. (Box 122)